[{"answer": "You can't do it very often.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "What's it like to give away $1 billion?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Are you nervous?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's just, if you look at the country and then you look at what we came out of, you know, and this is with the administration before this, it was very, very difficult.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "What is going on in America right now that is preventing more Tyler Perrys coming through, because clearly, they're not coming through in the same number?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Well, for me, I -- I can tell you this, and this may not be good advice for every person that's out of work, but for a lot of people, what I've found, and even when I was going through and homeless and trying to find a job and all those things, sometimes it means that you ought to try something else, something different, something new, because there were times in my life where I lost a lot.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "What is your advice for 23 million other Americans who are currently out of work and want a job?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "I'm not actually looking forward to the third one.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "What do you think is going to happen?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Well, unfortunately, I just -- being in the business that I'm in, which is show business, I realize that a lot of things is smoke and mirrors, a lot of this.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Why is it getting so fractured?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's awful that -- that it happened.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "What did you think of that?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "ERRY: Well, I think about it this way.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "Can any president deserve four more years if those two big figures loom large for the electorate?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "That's very interesting question.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Is America more or less racist after four years of its first black president?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "I don't -- first of all, I don't think it's healthy.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Is that helpful?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Oh, abused his entire life.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "He had been abused?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "I found it out by asking questions, finally, of him, because I was talking to him --", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "How did you find this out?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "He told me a lot about it.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "So, he told you?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Yes, he's still alive.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Is he still alive, your father?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "We don't speak very much, but I am taking care of him.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "And what kind of relationship do you have with him?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Absolutely, 100 percent.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "You support him?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "No, I never felt that.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Do you think despite the way that he -- he manhandled you and beat you and so on, did you feel that he loved you?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "-- so that was another thing I didn't know, which caused a lot of issues, as well.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "I did, about four years ago I asked, why.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "Did you have that out with him?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "No, he hasn't.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Has he ever said sorry?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "At this point, I don't know if it matters.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Would you like him to?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "She -- it -- well, you mean of all the success?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "-- get her a red Jaguar?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Just -- she's speechless, just a thank you and the love.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "What did she say to you?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "You don't know me.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Who you think you're talking to, old lady?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Yes, never --", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "ORGAN: Did you ever think, when you were young and you -- you thought of treading the boards that one day you'd be world famous for cross dressing?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "It's about strong women.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "There are lots of other Madeas from every -- I've met a Jewish Madea, I've met an Italian Madea, you know?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Any comment?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "I just try -- it drives me insane.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "You feel uncomfortable talking about money?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "No, who wants to show -- it's not a -- it's certainly not about showing off.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "-- show off about it?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Again, the best thing which is -- which changed my entire life was being able to support my mother.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "What is the best thing about money, though, for you?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Because I just feel that to whom much is given, much is required.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Why do you -- why do you feel awkward talking about this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "My faith.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "How have you avoided the pitfalls that go with superstar fame, big money and all the rest of it?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "I know everything, Tyler.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "How do you know that?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "You supplied the plane, didn't you?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Take another break, Tyler.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "What is this, that this woman's life is not worth a moment of silence?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "I actually did.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Do you enjoy playing the action hero?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "That's what Oprah said to me.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Because there are", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "I think we were both very young.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "And what went wrong?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Was it, in the end, your decision to walk away?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Do you regret that?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "Yeah, because we both were in a place where -- I just realized I should not have said this because -- I should not have said this.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "You thought it was the right thing?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Because I said too much.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Why shouldn't you have said it?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "What's the rush?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Don't you want little Tylers running around?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "I need a shot of vodka, my friend.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Do you want a glass of water?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "I'm fine.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "Who do you think's going to win?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "I'd say a little bit.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "Are you surprised how powerful television has now become?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "If he gets elected.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "Does he deserve a second term?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "For me, he has.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "Has he done enough, do you think?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "I want to see the best man win.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "What do you want to see from whoever wins in three weeks time?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "Well, I think we spend to much money on the military.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "How can a president smartly revive things do you think?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "What it did was, more than just itself, it set a precedent for so many other people to give money while they are young and vibrant and alive, not after they die.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 763, "question": "Pretty extraordinary thing to have done, to give a billion dollars of your own money away, right?", "qSentId": 762}, {"answer": "I think the global policeman should be the United Nations.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 775, "question": "What should America be doing?", "qSentId": 774}, {"answer": "Well, what -- no, I think it's -- I think it's good, because it's so clear that we're programmed and we're born to love and help each other, not to kill each other, to destroy each other.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "That's shocking, isn't it?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121019pmt", "aSentId": 794, "question": "Are you pleased with how the money is being used?", "qSentId": 793}]